

# Ronaldo Pangarego

# Fullstack Developer

### Profile

I am a fast learner, organized, and creative. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, and I have experience developing information system applications using the skills I have. I am also interested in learning UI / UX Design. I am also able to adapt quickly and think creatively as part of a team.

### Contact

Pontianak, Indonesia



rpangarego@gmail.com



<u>rpangarego.netlify.app</u>

# Experience

### Web Developer

2020 - Present

#### **Freelance**

- Create web system information application based on client needs using PHP and Bootstrap.

### **Graphic Designer**

2017-2018

#### **LINE Creator**

- Design stickers and themes for LINE messaging app.

# Organization

- Member of BPM Senat Mahasiswa STMIK Widya Dharma Pontianak (2018 - 2019)
- Member of Senat Mahasiswa STMIK Widya Dharma Pontianak (2017 - 2018)

### Education

Formal

**Universitas Widya Dharma Pontianak** S.Kom | Information Systems - GPA 3.68

2015 - 2020

#### **SMA Santo Paulus Pontianak**

2012 - 2015

Informal

Fullstack Javascript Developer

November 2020

BuildWithAngga

**Laravel Web Development** 

October 2020

SanberCode Indonesia

May 2020

# Fullstack Web Designer

BuildWithAngga

# Languages

- Indonesia
- English

## Skills

- Programming Languages HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP
- Frameworks/Libraries

Bootstrap, MaterialUI, ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, and Laravel

Database

MySQL, MongoDB and Firebase

Tools

VSCode, Sublime Text3, Git, Github, Adobe Illustrator, and Figma